this wasn't a plan when i first got into
working out and honestly my goal working
out was not to be
in the most greatest shape and to be
healthy and everything it was just to
get the girls and then you know one
thing turns into another and like i
remember spending about six years after
that that was about 2003
and i remember that next maybe five
years five to six years i was just
trying to figure out like how to get
ripped how to get abs how to do this and
do that i boxed i was i became an
amateur boxer i was doing a whole lot of
different things i even was a mailman at
the time and being a mailman you have to
deliver mail all day long you know go up
and down stairs so i turned that into
like a workout and uh about maybe it was
uh december 2008 a guy
i knew uh told me i should do a
bodybuilding show by the name of ken
hensley it took me six years to try to
figure out it took me eight weeks to do
i i i found the
love for just transformation and how
that transformation not only just
inspired and changed my body but it
changed my life it gave me a form of
discipline it gave me it made me
understand consistency sacrifice it made
me understand what ethic really is
because to do that crazy transformation
in such a short period of time it takes
a big amount of consistency and
discipline and also sacrifice and then
from then on you know started training
people because i felt like you know what
i can change myself i could probably
change others as well so quit my job at
the postal service started working at um
a gym went from making twenty two
dollars and twenty dollars and ten cent
hours to it seven dollars and fifty cent
per session just to make up for that
time i started to like train 16 17
people a day sun up to sundown which was
a lot i remember getting a call from a
guy named aaron williamson to train the
cast the fantastic four i was on set for
literally like a whole month
and i remember calling aaron saying you
know what i want this to be more than
just
a paycheck i want this to become a
career i was about to leave the set lord
behold who comes out the trailer michael
b joy they tell me to say you know he
might want to train because he's getting
ready for a movie called creed cree
me and mike worked out that first day
from then on it was like the brother
little brother always needed i was a big
brother he always won we've been
together ever since uh since 2014 um
coming up on our seventh year right now
and we've done everything together he
ever had any muscles it was me the diet
is different this time because he's not
only just fighting he's direct he has
the mental aspect of it that really goes
a big part of it because if the mental
is not in tune
then the body won't be into
the mind
and i i try to give him right now it's i
let him die at about he dies every day
because we getting closer to it but as
we started i just wanted him to make
healthy choices i just wanted to eat
healthy foods and try to stay away from
you know
fast foods and things like that it was
really just you know staying with
healthy foods and learning and actually
feeding the body eating every two and a
half three hours because your body needs
that few to be able to do the things
that it needs to do of course i go to
you know low carbohydrate playing with
plant carbohydrates water intake sodium
certain proteins i can't say okay we're
gonna eat this for six weeks because the
body started changing so i'm always like
making small you know just small changes
and choosing this instead of choosing
that as we continue to go every day so
as i got older i realized that you don't
have to spend two and a half hours in
the gym you can spend 30 minutes in the
gym 25 minutes in the gym because what
you're doing at that time that's gonna
get you the results that you want and
because he's doing so much he's like
maybe we do 25 minutes in the morning
keep boxing the day for like 30 minutes
do a quick 20 minute session after that
maybe another 20 minute session at
nighttime so we're getting that hour of
time we'll be doing the small spurts
because
i need him to be able to function and be
a director and an actor as well my
training philosophy to change of course
i went into the sport as a bodybuilder
and i don't really understand like you
know mobility and functionality of the
body we just got to look good now as as
i get older i'm understanding the true
science of the body and how to make the
mo the mobility of the body not just
being a muscle here i'm learning how to
use my body in different ways i'm doing
all kind of training from of course you
know i'm psyches now um i'm preparing to
do a triathlon soon i'm still doing you
know my bodybuilding aesthetic type of
training but more hit training across
this time like i'm i'm doing it all and
also learning about nutrition how to eat
healthy to to to to fuel the body not
just to make the body look like it needs
to look the body's always evolving so it
works a long time ago
it won't work right now 3-3 is going to
be great um there's somebody else that's
in 3 that's that i've been training he's
going to shock the world uh
y'all might know the other person in the
movie
jonathan majors what he's going to look
like what i have him looking like
oh boy for this one i said i want both
boxes to look like this is
a movie like 300 or something
you're going to see two warriors
fighting i've trained so many different
people i'm on so many movies i'm in
movies now it's like
i'm doing something in fitness that's
never been done and i feel like i'm
doing it the right way
i feel like i'm just getting started
[Music]
you